adsiduous.com 2018-10-16

# Privacy Policy | Adsiduous.com

### Privacy Policy

This page sets forth the privacy policies and practices of Adsiduous (“Adsiduous”) corporate site www.adsiduous.com (“Adsiduous Site”). The information collection practices of all of the Adsiduous companies and divisions are detailed by the privacy policies found on such entities’ websites. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully since by visiting this site and sharing information with Adsiduous you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy unless you offer different terms which are accepted by Adsiduous. in writing.To the extent there is a conflict between the terms of this Privacy Policy and a written agreement to which Adsiduous is party, the terms of such agreement shall prevail with respect to the parties to that agreement. For more information about Adsiduous and other Adsiduous companies please visit www.adsiduous.com.

STATEMENT OF RESPONSIBLE ONLINE MARKETING

Adsiduous information usage practices are based on two beliefs: first, that protecting user privacy is essential to the growth and prosperity of the Internet; second, that a personalized web experience can provide significant benefits to Internet end users if done properly. In accordance with these beliefs, Adsiduous creates results for advertisers and publishers in revolutionary ways without compromising individual privacy.If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, email us at info@adsiduous.com.

I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT, CONSUMER CHOICE AND ACCESS

Adsiduous is the corporate entity that manages the Adsiduous marketing and technology companies and divisions. Adsiduous Site is not directed towards individual Internet consumers nor does it seek any personally identifiable information (“PII”) from such consumers for marketing purposes. The only PII that may be collected is when a consumer seeks information from Adsiduous and contacts Adsiduous on his/her own accord by e-mail or through a contact form or otherwise.Like most standard website servers, we use log files to collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, platform type, third party web analytic tools, and date/time stamp. We use the information to analyze site usage, administer the site, understand usage and navigation trends in aggregate, and determine the relevance of content.Adsiduous may use cookies to collect data from this website to enable it to more effectively match advertisements to your interests. You can delete these cookies any time from your computer by following the instructions on this page: <http://www.aboutcookies.org/DEFAULT.ASPX?page=2> (opens in a new tab)

II. INFORMATION MANAGEMENT 

Adsiduous may share information with its affiliated entities for or in connection with the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial asset, reorganization or liquidation of any of the Adsiduous companies. Adsiduous also may release information when we believe release is appropriate to respond to a subpoena or otherwise comply with the law; enforce or apply our agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Adsiduous or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

III. SECURITY 

Adsiduous employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of data. Adsiduous has contracts in place with its customers in relation to their data, which data is handled in accordance with such agreements or as otherwise agreed upon by such parties. Adsiduous routinely evaluates its data security practices to identify security threats or opportunities for improvement.No transmission of data over the Internet, however, is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Adsiduous to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your information, Adsiduous cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with us.

IV. CONSENT AND CHANGES 

Adsiduous may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

VII. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, THIRD PARTY INFORMATION & LANGUAGE

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER THE PRIVACY OF ADSIDUOUS DATA OR ADSIDUOUS’S PRACTICES IS SUBJECT TO THE PROVISIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND ANY APPLICABLE TERMS AND CONDITIONS (WHICH MAY INCLUDE LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES AND/OR ARBITRATION OF DISPUTES). YOU AGREE THAT ADSIDUOUS’S LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE GREATER OF THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY ADSIDUOUS OR $250 TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS. YOU FURTHER AGREE THAT THIS AGREEMENT IS GOVERNED BY WASHINGTON LAW WITHOUT REGARD TO CHOICE OF LAW PRINCIPLES AND THAT ANY ACTION ARISING FROM OR RELATED TO THIS POLICY WILL BE EXCLUSIVELY VENUED IN A STATE OR FEDERAL COURT IN WASHINGTON.

You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to Adsiduous with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party’s personal data has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party’s personal data; (c) which of the third party’s data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. It is the express will of the parties that this agreement and all related documents have been drawn up in English.  

CONTACT US For more information or if you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at info@adsiduous.com.
